A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Dolley Madison Library, 1971; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-7
- Dolley Madison Library, 1976; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-8
- Dolley Madison Library, 1976; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-9
- Dolley Madison Library, International Worm Race, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-10
- Dolley Madison Library, International Worm Race, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-11
- Dolley Madison Library, International Worm Race, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-12
- Dolley Madison Library, International Worm Race, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-13
- Dolley Madison Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-DM-14
- Engleside Library, before completion, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-1
- Engleside Library, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-2
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-3
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-4
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-5
- Engleside Library, Dedication, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-6
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-7
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-8
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-9
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-10
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-11
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-12
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-13
- Engleside Library, Opening Day, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-14
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-15
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-16
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-17
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-18
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-19
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-20
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-21
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-22
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-23
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-24
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-25
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-26
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-27
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-28
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-29
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-30
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-31
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-32
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-33
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-34
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-35
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-36
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-37
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-38
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-39
- Engleside Library, 1973; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-40
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-41
- Engleside Library, Reopening, 1973 May 22; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-EN-42
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-1
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-2
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-3
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-4
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-5
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-6
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-7
- Fair Oaks Library, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FO-8
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Adult Reading Area, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-1
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Adult Reference Area, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-2
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Business and Technical Reference Area, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-3
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Technical Processing, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-4
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Technical Processing (Print Shop), Bob Sutphin, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-5
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Meeting Room (Seats 100), 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-6
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Director's Office, Mary K. McCulloch, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-7
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Virginia Room, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-8
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Conference Room and Library Board Room, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-9
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Loading Dock and Bookmobile Garage, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-10
- Fairfax City Regional Library, William L. Whitesides Inauguration party, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-11
- Fairfax City Regional Library, William L. Whitesides Inauguration party, 1970 March; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-12
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Circulation Desk, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-13
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Business and Technical Reference Area, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-14
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Business and Technical Reference Area, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-15
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Virginia Room, 1972; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-16
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-17
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-18
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-19
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, Dr. Paullin (in red) and Dr. Piston Library Board Members, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-20
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, Dr. Paullin (in red) and Dr. Piston Library Board Members, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-21
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-22
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, L to R: Audrey Cratsley, Jay Watson, Pat Carey, 1972 July 12; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-23
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-24
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-25
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Miriam Marshall, Children's librarian, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-26
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-27
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-28
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Miriam Marshall, Children's librarian (standing), 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-29
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-30
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-31
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-32
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-33
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-34
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-35
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-36
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Book Catalogues, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-37
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Anita Lamkin and Harva Sheeler, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-38
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-39
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-40
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-41
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-42
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Virginia Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-43
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Virginia Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-44
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Virginia Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-45
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Circulation Desk, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-46
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-47
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-48
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-49
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-50
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-51
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Banner Happening 4th of July, Children's Room, 1973 June 25; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-52
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Exterior, 1976; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-53
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Friends Book Sale, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-54
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Friends Book Sale, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-55
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Friends Book Sale, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-56
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Friends Book Sale, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-57
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Friends Book Sale, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-58
- Fairfax City Regional Library, temporarily closed sign, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-59
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Poetry Reading program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-60
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Genealogy program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-61
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Genealogy program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-62
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Clown at children's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-63
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Clown at children's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-64
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Clown at children's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-65
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Library skill's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-66
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Library skill's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-67
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Library skill's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-68
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Library skill's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-69
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Library skill's program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-70
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Entrance, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-71
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Entrance, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-72
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Adult Reading Room and Reference Area, 1963; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-73
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Interior, 1970; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-74
- Fairfax City Regional Library, 10th Anniversary, 1972 July 6; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-75
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Audiovisual Department, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-76
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-77
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-78
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-79
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Glenn Martin, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-80
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Joy Sibley, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-81
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Musical Concordia, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-82
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Young Soloist Concert, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-83
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Sandy Hiller at piano, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-84
- Fairfax City Regional Library, Music program, Undated; Box 2: FXCO-LIB-FX-85
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-1
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-2
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-3
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-4
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-5
- George Mason Regional Library, Meeting Room, 1967; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-6
- George Mason Regional Library, Mrs. Vorhis registers new patron, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-7
- George Mason Regional Library, Mr. Burch, Mrs. Corbett, Mrs. Schneider at Circulation Desk (L to R), 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-8
- George Mason Regional Library, Students using the photocopier, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-9
- George Mason Regional Library, Ginny Baker (page) shelving books, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-10
- George Mason Regional Library, "Dimming the lights" Mrs. Schneider beyond candle, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-11
- George Mason Regional Library, Mrs. Edna Rutkans, branch librarian at Reference Desk, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-12
- George Mason Regional Library, Circulation Desk, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-13
- George Mason Regional Library, Circulation Desk, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-14
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-15
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-16
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-17
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-18
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-19
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-20
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-21
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-22
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-23
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-24
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-25
- George Mason Regional Library, Tax Counselling, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-26
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-27
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-28
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-29
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-30
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-31
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-32
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-33
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-34
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-35
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-36
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-37
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-38
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-39
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-40
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-41
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-42
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-43
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-44
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-45
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-46
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-47
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-48
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-49
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-50
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-51
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-52
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-53
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-54
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-55
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-56
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-57
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-58
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-59
- George Mason Regional Library, "Growing Up" program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-60
- George Mason Regional Library, Ad Ed program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-61
- George Mason Regional Library, Ad Ed program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-62
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-63
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-64
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-65
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-66
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-67
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-68
- George Mason Regional Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-69
- George Mason Regional Library, Fairfax Symphony Orchestra program, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-70
- George Mason Regional Library, Tim Burch and patron in Children's Room, 1973 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-71
- George Mason Regional Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-72
- George Mason Regional Library, Summer Reading, 1979 June; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-73
- George Mason Regional Library, Summer Reading, 1979 June; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GM-74
- Great Falls Library, Sign, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-1
- Great Falls Library, Exterior, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-2
- Great Falls Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-3
- Great Falls Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-4
- Great Falls Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-5
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-6
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-7
- Great Falls Library, Storytime, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-8
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-9
- Great Falls Library, Child and Mother, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-10
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-11
- Great Falls Library, Shelves, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-12
- Great Falls Library, Child and Parent, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-13
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-14
- Great Falls Library, Child patron, 1983; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-15
- Great Falls Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-GF-16
- Herndon Fortnightly Library, Open House, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-HE-1
- Herndon Fortnightly Library, Interior, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-HE-2
- Herndon Fortnightly Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-HE-3
- Herndon Fortnightly Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-HE-4
- John Marshall Library, Storefront, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-1
- John Marshall Library, Storefront, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-2
- John Marshall Library, Storefront, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-3
- John Marshall Library, Storefront, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-4
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-5
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-6
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-7
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-8
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-9
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-10
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-11
- John Marshall Library, Interior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-12
- John Marshall Library, Sign marking future site of new branch with Sup. Joe Alexander, 1971; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-13
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-14
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-15
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, 1974; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-16
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-17
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-18
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-19
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Library Board Chairman Kenneth A. Meiklejohn, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-20
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-21
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-22
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-23
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-24
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-25
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Richard Marshall - John Marshall descendant and others, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-26
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Library Board member Gladys Keating, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-27
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, BOS Chairman Jean Packard, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-28
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Lee District Supervisor Joe Alexander, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-29
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Library Director William L. Whitesides, Jessie Mullins, former Library Board member, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-30
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-31
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-32
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-33
- John Marshall Library, Sign, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-34
- John Marshall Library, Huntley Meadows Program, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-35
- John Marshall Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-36
- John Marshall Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-37
- John Marshall Library, Youth Art Month, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-38
- John Marshall Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-39
- John Marshall Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-40
- John Marshall Library, Interior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-41
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-42
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-43
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-44
- John Marshall Library, Adult Ed., Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-45
- John Marshall Library, Adult Ed., Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-46
- John Marshall Library, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-47
- John Marshall Library, Talking Books, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-48
- John Marshall Library, Child reading book, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-49
- John Marshall Library, Child reading book, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-50
- John Marshall Library, Child reading book, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-51
- John Marshall Library, Child reading book, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-52
- John Marshall Library, Child reading book, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-53
- John Marshall Library, Exterior, Undated; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-54
- John Marshall Library, Sign marking future site of new branch with Sup. Joe Alexander, 1971; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-55
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, Congressman Herb Harris, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-56
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-57
- John Marshall Library, Dedication, 1975 February 23; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-JM-58
- Kings Park Library, Under construction, National Bank of Fairfax in foreground, 1972 May; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-KP-1
- Kings Park Library, Under construction, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-KP-2
- Kings Park Library, Under construction, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-KP-3
- Kings Park Library, Under construction, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-KP-4
- Kings Park Library, Under construction, 1972; Box 3: FXCO-LIB-KP-5